{
    "levels":
    [
        {
            "level": 1,
            "levelUp": 3,
            "problems":
            [
                {
                    "problem": "15 + 9",
                    "solution": 24
                },
                {
                    "problem": "20 + 2",
                    "solution": 22
                },
                {
                    "problem": "11 + 1",
                    "solution": 12
                },
                {
                    "problem": "5 + 6",
                    "solution": 11
                },
                {
                    "problem": "4 + 2",
                    "solution": 6
                },
                {
                    "problem": "9 + 10",
                    "solution": 19
                },
                {
                    "problem": "80 + 1",
                    "solution": 81
                },
                {
                    "problem": "9 + 90",
                    "solution": 99
                },
                {
                    "problem": "8 + 9",
                    "solution": 17
                },
                {
                    "problem": "8 + 10",
                    "solution": 18
                },
                {
                    "problem": "17 + 9",
                    "solution": 26
                },
                {
                    "problem": "16 + 9",
                    "solution": 25
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": 2,
            "problems":
            [
                
            ]
        }
    ]
}